[SLOW COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING]
Ugh. I cannot believe Christy let Howard
into my apartment.
And I cannot believe people pay
for horoscopes...
...but on a more serious note,
it's 8:13 and we're still not playing "Halo."
Okay, fine. We'll just play one-on-one
until he gets back.
One-on-one? We don't play one-on-one.
We play teams, not one-on-one.
One-on-one.
(Leonard:)Well, the only way we can play teams
at this point is if we cut Raj in half.
(Raj:)Sure, cut the foreigner in half.
There's a billion more where he came from.
(Penny:)Hey, if you guys need a fourth, I'll play.
(Sheldon:)- Great idea.
- Uh, no.
(Sheldon:)The wheel was a great idea.
Relativity was a great idea.
(Sheldon:)This is a notion,
and a rather sucky one at that.
- Why?
- Why? Oh...
(Sheldon:)- Penny, Penny, Penny.
- What, what, what?
(Sheldon:)This is a complex battle simulation
with a steep learning curve.